now in terms of of cyber
security listen everything that we
accuse the Iranians of doing and the
North Koreans of doing and the Chinese
of doing we do literally every single
day that's why we have NSA nsa's job
isn't just to intercept Communications
electronic communications it's also to
disrupt cyber networks that's what they
get paid to do so this self-
flagellation and victimhood just doesn't
fly yes of course we need better cyber
security but everybody else needs better
cyber security against us too so this
this ongoing drum beat of complaints
over cyber security just doesn't do
anything for me it just seems to be it
just seems to be empty